cgu.edu 2019-07-08

# Privacy Policy - Claremont Graduate University

Claremont Graduate University uses cookies and web analytics services to track user activity on the institution’s main website. This information is used to track overall usage and trends in user behavior; we do not track specific users. By using this website, you agree that we can place cookies on your device and track usage on www.cgu.edu.

While visiting this website or filling out an information form on an affiliated website, app, or advertisement, a user may choose to provide personal information through web forms, email, or other electronic means. Any personally identifiable information submitted will be used only for the purpose(s) indicated. Claremont Graduate University does not sell or lease any personal data submitted by users to anyone. Nor does Claremont Graduate University disclose to third parties any personal data submitted by users without the user’s consent, except as required by law.

We will use the information you give us to respond to you, regarding the reason you contacted us. We will not share your information with any third party outside of our organization, other than as necessary to fulfill your request.

Unless you ask us not to, we may contact you via email in the future to tell you about our programs or changes to this privacy policy.

### Your Access to and Control Over Information

You may opt out of any future contacts from us at any time. You can do the following at any time by contacting us via email at [privacy@cgu.edu](mailto:privacy@cgu.edu) or the phone number given below:

  * See what data we have about you, if any.
  * Change/correct any data we have about you.
  * Have us delete any data we have about you.
  * Express any concern you have about our use of your data.

The Claremont Graduate University main website may contain links to other websites which are independently run outside of the cgu.edu domain. The University is not responsible for the privacy practices, activities, or content of such independent sites. Neither those sites, nor any content available through links from them, are screened, reviewed, or endorsed by Claremont Graduate University.
